qualifio.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy – Privacy & Terms – Qualifio

**At Qualifio, we’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.**

We want you to know how we work and why we need your data. This Privacy Policy explains when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our website, how we use it and the conditions under which we may disclose it to others.

## 1\. General

This Privacy Policy applies to all personal data (hereinafter the “data”) that we collect about you for the purposes of delivering the services we offer.

Your use of our website or transmission of your data to us when making a purchase means that you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the provisions of this policy, please do not use our site or transmit your data to us. In that case, however, you accept that you shall be unable to access any of the services and other benefits offered by Qualifio.

## 2\. Contact details of the data processing manager

Qualifio S.A. (hereinafter: “Qualifio”) having its registered office at Place de l’Université 16, 1348 Louvain-la-Neuve and being registered at the Banque-Carrefour des Entreprises under registration number (BE) 0822.741.924., is responsible for processing the personal data (hereinafter the “data”) that you provide to us directly on our site: www.qualifio.com.

## 3\. What data do we gather, for what purposes, and on what legal basis?

### 3.1 The data we collect directly from you

We collect the data that you send us:

#### (i) via our Website, particularly when you use the “Request a demo” tab, or when you use a contact form.

We use this data (i.e.) your surname, forenames, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, language, the city and country in which you live, your company name, its sector and the countries in which it operates, along with your position in your company) so that we can get back to you with the most relevant information possible. (consent)

Usually, items of data with an asterisk against them are mandatory. If this information is not provided, we shall not be able to get back to you about your request.

#### (ii) when you sign up for our “newsletter”

When you sign up for our newsletter, we use your e-mail address to keep you informed about our products and services, as well as to send you ideas for your forthcoming campaigns, to tell you about our customers’ typical experiences and successes, and also to let you know about market trends.

You can withdraw your consent at any time, either by writing to us or by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link that can be found in the e-mails that we send you.

#### (iii) on our website when you use the “Connection” tab

When you log onto our website, we use your data to give you access to Qualifio Manager, the Qualifio platform’s back office. When using Qualifio Manager, your data is used and stored in order to optimise your experience on the Qualifio platform in terms of access to your campaigns and statistics, administration of user rights, etc.

If you contact our Helpdesk (or vice versa), we shall use your surname, forename, e-mail address and company name in order to process your request and to provide you with the best possible service (fulfilment of the contract to which you are a signatory, or accomplishment of pre-contractual procedures).

*  
**

Qualifio shall process your data only to the extent necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

### 3.2 The data we collect when you interact with the site

Our site uses “cookies”. By using it, you agree to accept cookies on your computer, tablet or smartphone. It is through the use of cookies that we can offer you the best browsing experience on our site (for example, they help us remember your preferences when you visit the site.

We recommend that you view our “Cookie Policy”, which can be found on our website. This will give you more information on this type of technology and your related rights.

## 4\. How long do we keep your data for?

We keep your data for the period required to complete the activities for which it was gathered, but no longer than the limit stipulated by the applicable legislation.

## 5\. Who can we send your data to?

In order to provide our services effectively, we may need to subcontract some tasks, in whole or in part, to technical subcontractors with whom we have entered into contracts (e.g. the subcontractors responsible for maintaining our infrastructure, IT security, hosting, marketing tools, helpdesk and others).

Qualifio requires its subcontractors to adhere to data protection legislation and to submit satisfactory guarantees on the implementation of appropriate technical and organisational measures. They are required to demonstrate that their processing system complies with current data protection legislation and that your rights are guaranteed.

We do not sell or in any way disclose to third parties the data that we gather about you. However, if we have a legal obligation, or if a court ruling requires us to do so, we shall pass on your data to the extent necessary to comply with this law or court ruling.

Under certain circumstances, our website and our apps will provide you with plug-ins for various social networks. If you choose to interact with social network sites such as Facebook or Twitter (for example by setting up an account), your activity on our site or via our apps will also be accessible on that social network site. If you are logged onto one of these social network sites during your visit to any of our sites or apps, or if you interact with any of the social network plug-ins, the social network site may also add this information to your profile on that network, depending on your privacy protection settings. If you want to prevent this type of data transfer, please log off your social network site before logging on to any of our sites or apps, or change the app privacy protection settings, if possible. Please read these social networks’ own privacy protection policies for further details on the collection and transmission of personal data, on your rights, and on how you can achieve a satisfactory degree of privacy protection.

We use a third-party messaging service provider, MailChimp, to send you our e-mails. So that we can send e-mails via MailChimp, we provide MailChimp with certain information, i.e. your e-mail address, your name, your language and your country. MailChimp processes the information on you in accordance with the provisions of its [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/). MailChimp also uses certain types of technology such as pixels and invisible pixels (“web beacons”) in e-mails sent by MailChimp. This technology tells MailChimp whether you have opened or clicked on our e-mails and, if so, the date, time and IP address used when opening or clicking on them. For further information on the use of this technology by MailChimp, please read their [Cookie Statement](https://mailchimp.com/legal/cookies/).

We also use a third-party popup solution, WisePops, to display tailored messages to you and request some of your personal details during your navigation on qualifio.com/blog. You can find more information about the [details WisePops collects on this page](https://support.wisepops.com/more-info/data-and-cookie-policy).

## 6\. What rights do you have?

### 6.1 Right of access

You have the right to, at any time, view your data free of charge by sending an e-mail to dpo@qualifio.com or a letter to Qualifio’s registered office at Place de l’Université 16, 1348 Louvain-la-Neuve.

### 6.2 Right of correction

You have the right to demand the correction or deletion of any data that is incorrect, inappropriate or no longer required by sending an e-mail to dpo@qualifio.com or by sending a written request by post to Qualifio’s registered office at Place de l’Université 16, 1348 Louvain-la-Neuve.

Please note that you are at all times obliged to ensure that the data you send us is accurate.

### 6.3 Right to be forgotten

When you no longer want your data to be processed and you meet the conditions to invoke the right of deletion under data protection law, we shall delete your data from our database.

### 6.4 Right of portability

Where necessary, you also have the right to have your data transferred under the terms laid down in applicable data protection law.

### 6.5 Right of objection

You have the right to object to any use of your data for marketing purposes. You can exercise your right to object either via the automated procedures provided for that purpose in the e-mail sent to you or, failing that, by sending an e-mail to the following address: [dpo@qualifio.com](mailto:dpo@qualifio.com).

### 6.6 Right of restriction of processing

Finally, you have the right to require Qualifio to restrict the processing of your data, as provided for in applicable data protection legislation.

## 7\. Information regarding children

As a general rule, we do not intentionally gather personal information relating to children under 13 years of age. If we discover that we have inadvertently gathered information on children aged under 13 years of age, we shall take steps to delete the information as soon as possible, unless applicable law requires us to retain it.

When we know that a child is over 13 years of age but is considered to be a minor under applicable law, we shall obtain permission from the parents or guardian before using that child’s personal information.

## 8\. Links to other websites and services

Our websites may contain links to third-party sites, and some of our services give you access to third-party services such as social networks.

We have no control over the way in which those sites and services process your personal information. We do not check these third-party sites and services, and we are not responsible for these third-party sites or services or their privacy protection practices. Please read the privacy statements on the third-party sites or services that you access via our sites or services.

## 9\. Security

We have introduced appropriate technical and organisational security rules designed to avoid the destruction, loss, falsification, amendment, unauthorised access to or accidental disclosure of data to third parties, together with any unauthorised processing of the data.

## 10\. Limitation of liability clause

Qualifio’s liability shall be restricted to direct harm, to the exclusion of any indirect loss. Qualifio can never be held liable for harm deemed to be indirect such as, without this list being exhaustive, loss of data, financial or commercial loss, loss of profits, increased general costs, or disruption of planning or scheduling.

Moreover, Qualifio cannot be held liable for any harm arising from any unlawful manipulation of the data by third parties, such as data theft, introduction of viruses, hacking or any other IT malpractices.

We should also highlight the fact that links to our website may contain hypertext links and other references to other sites that we do not manage or control, to which these provisions do not apply. We are not responsible for the content of such websites or the offers, products or services that they contain. We recommend that you carefully read the privacy protection rules of each site that you visit, as those rules may differ from the rules set out here.

## 11\. What happens in the event of disputes?

If you think that we have failed in any of our legal and/or contractual obligations, please send us an e-mail to dpo@qualifio.com. We shall do everything we can to follow it up as soon as possible.

All complaints, claims or grievances should be submitted to Qualifio’s registered office.

If you are not satisfied with our response, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

## 12\. Applicable law and competent courts

These provisions are to be governed, interpreted and fulfilled in accordance with the laws of Belgium. Belgian law alone shall apply in the event of disputes.

All disputes that cannot be settled amicably within a time limit of one month from their occurrence, unless this limit is extended by mutual agreement, may be brought by either party before the French language courts of the Walloon Brabant region. Those courts alone shall have jurisdiction.

## 13\. Effective date

This policy was created and brought into force on February 1, 2018. We reserve the right to, entirely at our discretion, change or amend parts of this policy to add parts to it or to remove parts at any time. We will keep you updated of any such changes either by e-mail or via a notice on our website.
